To protect the knowledge I received from you, I abandoned speech.
Are you saying you will protect me, Chane?
I won't let them eat me!
I will have to eat them first!
To think it was alcohol...
This time we're gonna take care of the Martillo family!
不思議なもんですね…
人と人との出会いって
It sure is a mysterious thing,
how people meet.
All meetings might be somewhat of a miracle.
すベての出会いは
奇跡のようなものかもしれませんね
ええ ところでマイザ一さん
Yeah...
By the way, Mr. Maiza...
さっきの傷 何でそんなに
治りが早いんですか?
Why did your wound heal so fast?
差し支えないなら
教えてもらえないですか?
If it's not too much of a burden to you, can you tell me?
いつかは お話できる時が
来るかもしれませんが
I might be able to tell you sometime, but...
今はまだ…
I can't just yet.
そうですか…
I see...
あの女
That woman!
マイ ザ一さん ちよつと失礼します
Mr. Maiza, excuse me for a bit!
Firo!
フイ一ロ? お…
君は…
You are—
おい ちよっと待て
待てって言ってるだろ
Hey! Stop it!
I'm telling you to stop it!
まあ 落ち着けつて
Just calm down.
For now, I just want to give this to you.
とりあえず これ力ヾ
渡したいだけなんだ
ハハツ
はい 死体はー つだけです
Yes, there's only one corpse.
え? はい はい
Eh? Yes... Yes.
その男 シヤ一ネと互角に
渡り合ってるということだ
That must mean that man is fighting with Chane on even ground.
Shoot both of them when you get a chance.
そのスキに 2人とも撃て
りよ… 了解しました
Understood.
コ 一 ドぴ邑夕力ヾ発動 さ れ た
Code Beta has been put in motion.
本当にシヤ一ネさんを
殺すんですか?
Are we really going to kill Ms. Chane?!
白服と交戦中のスキを
狙えとのことだ
He told us to look for a chance now that she's fighting the white-suit.
その話さ一 詳しく
教えてくれねっかな一と!
Can you tell me a bit about the specifics of that story?!
ううつ!
Hey, hey, hey! Drop your gun!
ハイハイハイ 銃捨てて一
そこの気弱そうな君も
銃 捨てて~~
You weak-looking fellow, drop your gun as well.
おう… クソツ
Damn!
Oh, he ran away.
おやおや 逃げちや つたよ…
I won't call him a coward, though.
まあ 臆病たあ言ゎないさ
俺を見て逃げるのは
こりやすなわち 通常の反応だもんなあ
To see me and then run away is the natural thing to do, after all.
ううつ…
シヤ一ネつてのは あの女で
交戦する白服ってのは俺のことだろ?
Chane is that woman, and the white-suit she's fighting is me, right?
すごいな あの女 !
That woman is amazing!
俺のほうから
逃げたのなんて初めてだせ
This was the first time I've had to run away.
教えてくれねえかなあ…
Can't you tell me?
どうして お前ら
仲間のあいつを殺すんだ?
Why are you going to kill this friend of yours?
うつ うう うつ うう
ノチ工ス丿
どラする? このまま實ベごき
投ノプ髑レ ご逃ノプるか ‥
What should I do?
Should I throw all my plans out the window and run?
そんなゎけ仁も〔 )くま‥
I just can't do that.
甘め ご不死すの顔だけ さも
見 ごおヵ淘ば
I have to see the face of that other Immortal at the very least.
うつ?
お兄ちやん… 誰なの?
Mister, who are you?
Mister...
Who are you?
ねえ 返事してよ 僕は…
Hey, why don't you answer?
My name...
卜一マスだよ
is Thomas.
なぜウソをつく チ工ス君?
Why are you lying... Czes-kun?
チェスワフメイ工ル
Czeslaw Meyer...
どう して僕の名前を ?
How do you know my name?
ああ… お前がレイル卜レ一サ一 ?
You are Rail Tracer!
ほう… よく分かつたな
That's one sharp observation!
俺がレイル卜レ一サ一だ
I am Rail Tracer.
お前がガキじやないことも
I also know that you're no kid, and that you want to kill all the passengers,
乗客を殺したがつてることも
分かつてる
だから まあ… 殺しとく
so... I will kill you.
うつ! ぐ! くつく うぐ~ ぐ
真っ赤な怪物だと?
バ力な話で お茶を濁すつもりか?
A deep-red monster?
Are you trying to mislead us with some stupid story to cover your tracks?
ウソじゃねえって! ほんとに
この列車には化け物が乗ってんだよ!
I'm not lying!
There's really a monster riding on board this train!
うつ うつ うう
よう! シヤ一ネちや~ん
Hey, Chane-chan!
お前 実は黒服の連中に
嫌われてんだつてなぁ?
I heard, in reality, you are hated by those black-suits,
and that you hate them as well,
お前も連中のことが
嫌いなんだつてなあ?
で お前 ヒユ一イ'
ラフォレツ 卜様とやらの
that you're the favorite pupil of Huey Laforet, and...
一番のお気に入りで
お前もその信者なんだつてなあ?
that you're a devotee of his.
And to top it all off, they said that Huey is immortal as well!
おまけに そのヒユ一イ様とやらは
不死身なんだってなぁ?
み一んな こいつが
お話してくれたぜ
This guy told me all about it.
Right?
"Yeah, yeah."
Do you realize that the black-suits are trying to kill you?
お前さあ 黒服伸間に狙われてるって
気づいてるか?
あいつら どさくさに紛れて
あんたを殺すつもりらしいぜ
They were planning to kill you in the confusion between you and me.
お前 ほんとは この作戦に
反対なんだつて?
They said you were actually opposing their original plan?
人質取つたりするのが
イヤなんだつて?
That you didn't like to take hostages and such?
ヒユ一イってのは そもそも
そういうのをイヤがってたみてえだが
It looks like Huey didn't like such things from the start, but...
甘いよなあ そんな人間が
一番信用できねえ
You're too naive!
That's the kind of person you can't trust at all!
お前もさあ一
Aren't you, too...
just being used by that guy called Huey?!
そのヒユ一イつて奴に
だまされてるだけなんじゃねえの?
俺が この列車を降りたら
真っ先にやることを教えてやろうか?
Shall I tell you the first thing I'll do when I get off this train?
ヒユ一イラフオレツ 卜を殺す
I'm going to kill Huey Laforet!
正直 てめえを殺すのは
乗り気じゃねえのよ
To be honest, I didn't have any interest in killing you.
ほかの黒服どもは 自分は絶対に
死なねぇつてツラしてるから
Just because those black-suits thought they were never going to get killed, I felt like killing them...
殺しがいもあるけどよ
But you have this vibe that you're putting your life on the line for something...
お前は どこか
命かけてるっぽいからな
そこで俺は者えた !
So that's when I came to think of this...
お前の絶対的存在である ヒユ一イ
ラフォレツ 卜を殺してやったほうが
Wouldn't it be more interesting, then, if I killed this Huey Laforet, who is your absolute master?
おもしれえんじやねえかつてな !
オイオイオイ もう終わりかよ
Oh, oh, oh...
It's over already?
That's how it's gotta be!
そうこなくつちや
とにかく殺す!
不死身だろうが殺す!
I'll just kill him!
Even if he's immortal, I'll kill him...
お前の 目 の前でな !
right in front of you.
I will teach this laid-back, "I won't die, so I'm safe" fellow the harshness of life to the fullest!
死なないから自分が安全だなんて
思つてる ユルユル野郎に
人生の厳しさをイヤっ乙いうほど
教え込んでやるよお!
さあ どうするよ
シヤ一ネちやんよお!
Well, what will you do, Chane-chan?!
久しいなあ マイザ一アヴァ一ロ
It has been a while, Maiza Avaro.
Szilard!
セラ一ド!
It has been over 200 years since our parting on the Advena Avis.
いちベつ
アドウ工ナ'アウイス号で 一賽以来
実に二百数十年ぶ り だ
Who is that, Maiza?
そいつは誰だ? マイ ザ一
知り合いか?
An acquaintance of yours?
逃げて下さい
Run away, please.
What are you saying?
あ?
何 言つてんだ?
皆さん 何も言わず逃げて下さい
この男の狙いは私ー 人です
All of you, run away without a word.
I am the only one this guy needs.
いってえ誰なんだよ そいつは?
Who the hell is he?
この男は…
かつて私の伸間ー3人と
This man is the one who, at one point, killed thirteen of my friends...
as well my little brother.
私の弟を殺した人間です
その後 5人食ったから
正確にはー8人だがな
Since then I've eaten five more, so it's eighteen now, to be precise.
Szilard!
セラ一ド
何が何だか分からねえが
I don't know what's going on exactly, but...
つまりこいつは
マイ ザ一の敵つてわけだな?
In other words, this guy is Maiza's enemy, right?
じやあ 俺らの
敵ってことじゃねえか
Then... he's our enemy as well!
だあ…
何するんだ !
What are you doing?!
行かないで
無駄死にするだけです
Don't go!
You will only die in vain.
What?!
何だと?
マイザ一よお… 何で このジジイ
Maiza... Why... is this old man still standing?!
まだ立ってんだよ?
I will explain later,
理由は あとで説明しますから
とにかく逃げて下さい!
so please, just run for now!
That's a wise warning you're giving there...
賢明な忠告だ
だ力ヾ 一歩遅かつたな
However, you are just too late!
Don't make holes in the Conductor's room!
車掌室に穴を開けるな
耳をかすめただろうが
You grazed my ears!
分かつたら謝ること
If you understand, apologize.
At least say sorry or something.
ごめんなさいくらい言えよ
そり やすまなかつた ごめん
I was out of line there.
Sorry.
続けるといい
You two should continue.
I will kill the one who survives.
生き残つたほうを俺が殺す
Who are you?!
誰だよ お前
Don't mind me.
気に彗るな
しゃベる空気だとでも思ってくれ
Just letting you know I was in a talking mood.
空気ならしやベるんじやね一よ !
We're not in the mood for talking!
手厳しいな
You're so harsh.
You bitch!
このアマ !
お前さ さっきそいつが
言つてたこと本当か?
Are the things he said a while ago true?
ほら ほんとはこの作戦に反対だの
人はあまり殺したくないだの
You know, about you being against their plan...
That you don't really like to kill people...
That Huey doesn't really like to do that either and such.
ヒユ一イつて奴も
そういうのが嫌いだの
そうか ならいいや
I see.
That's all right then.
何だったらよ
ちょっと加勢してやろうか?
Shall I help you a bit then?
はあ? それつてちよつと
おかしくねえか?
Isn't that a little weird?
I don't really understand, but...
よく分からねえが 黒服と
俺らの仲間を殺して回つてるのは
aren't you the guy who's been going around killing my men and the black-suits?!
お前だろうがよお !
ああ でもよ
さつきのお前の話 聞くと…
Yeah, but you know...
When I heard your story just now...
実はいい奴つぽいじやん この女
Doesn't she seem like the good-guy type to you, this woman?
Stop screwing around, you monster!
ふざけんな 化け物!
てめえは あれか?
Are you... like that?!
戦場で銃を持ったガキが
向かってきたら
The kind of person who, when a kid holding a gun would come at them on the battlefield,
would try to save him rather than kill him?!
殺さないで助けちまうた鍾ゐ人間か?
どんなに恐ろしい怪物かと思ったら
唇鱒が出そうな偽善者じゃねえか!
Just when I was imagining what kind of monster you would be,
you turn out to be some kind of hypocrite that makes me want to puke!
I will save her, but what of it?
助けるけど 何か?
I think one can feel compassion exactly when it is within one's strength to do so.
そういう同情とかってのは
やっぱり余裕があるからこそ
できることだと思うワケよ
And I'm just like that,
その点 俺は大丈夫だ
なぜなら俺は絶対 殺されないからな
because I can't be killed, no matter what.
覚えておけ
Remember that.
甘さや同情ってのは
強者にだけ持ちうる特権だ
Pity and compassion are privileges that are reserved for the strong.
そして俺は…
And I am... strong!
強者だ
てめえはアレか?
So you're like that?
本当に自分は
死なないとでも思つてるのか?
You really think you can't die?
Of course.
無論だ… なぜなら世界は…
After all, the world is mine!
俺のものだからな
放せよ! 中に仲間がいるんだ!
Let me go!
My friends are in there!
ダメです! 今 中に入ったら…
I can't!
You can't go in now—
君は 何者だ?
Who exactly are you?
じじ
あの爺は何者なんだ?
Who is that old man?!
本当に お前は頭の悪い男だ
マイザ一
You really are one dumb fellow, Maiza.
あの時 欲をかかずに
わしにも知識を分け与えておけば
If only you had let go of your ambition and shared your knowledge with me,
then all this blood wouldn't have had to be spilled.
こうして血が流れずに
済んだものを
Szilard...
セラ一 ド
What's going on?
何事だ…
Don Martillo, please let us handle this.
ドンマ丿しテイ一ジヨ
ここは我々にお任せ下さい
あるいは うちの
もめ事のせいかもしれませんので
This might be a result of a dispute of ours, so...
しかし
But...
あなたに万が一があれば
フイ一ロに会わせる顔がありません
If anything should happen to you,
I won't be able to look Firo in the eye.
どうか お気を静めて下さい
Please stay calm.
Go take a look upstairs.
上を見てこい
And take a look at our office as well.
うちの事務所の様子もな
はい
Okay.
あいつらの仕返しだったら
どうしよう 三リア!
What if he came back for us, Miria?!
私たちのせいだよね !
It'd be our fault.
だとしたら この人たちに
申し訳ないぞ !
It would be so rude toward these people!
It's a problem of responsibility, right?!
責任問題だね !
なぜ そんなにあの薬にこだわる ?
Why are you so concerned with that medicine?
It's simple. I just want to know.
簡単なこと…
ただ 知りたいからだ
お前が覆い隠した あの薬の秘密を
解明するのが悲願でな
It has always been my desire to solve the secret of that medicine you have been hiding.
自分を殺せる人間を
増やすだけのことだろう?
I'd say you're only after the ability to kill more people!
That's not true.
そうでもない
私のやり方は極めて合理的でね
You see, my conduct is quite rational.
In other words, anyone who drinks that will become immortal?!
つまり あの酒を飲んだ人間は
不老不死になるつてのか?
マイ ザ一さんや あの爺も
不死身だと?
You're saying Mr. Maiza and that old man are immortal as well?
君は誰なんだ?
Who are you?
グレツ 卜から得た知識で
できそこないの薬を作つたのだ
With the knowledge obtained from Gerd, I managed to make a useless version of the medicine.
できそこない?
Useless?
It will make you immortal, but it won't prevent aging.
不老ではないが不死にはなる薬だ
それを強者に飲ませれば
完成品を飲んだ我々が
If we let those in power drink it, we, who have drunk the finished product, are able to one-sidedly eat those people.
一方的に連中を
食うことができる!
労せずして奴らの知識と能力を
得ることができるのだ
Then, we can sell their knowledge and power without aging ourselves.
Don't you think it's a swift and certain method?
迅速かつ確実な方法だとは
思わないかね?
人造人間? 君カヾ?
An artificial human? You are?
そして 私を造ったのが
あのセラ一ドです
And the one who created me is Szilard.
群体の別動コ口二一として
Like a self-acting colony of an Army,
Szilard can relay information to me.
私はセラ一ドから
知識を与えられることができます
逆にセラ一ドは私の細胞内部に
存在する 女性細胞の構成要素と
And the other way around,
Szilard can separate the individual female elements within my cells...
from the individual immortal cells Szilard has—
セラ一ドの不死細胞の構成要素を
分離させることが…
Wait, wait, wait!
待つた 待つた 待つた!
俺は頭が良くないんだ
簡単に言ってくれ
I'm not that smart.
Tell me in layman's terms.
In other words...
つまり…
一言で言えば
セラ一ドの意志によつて
In a few words, I am alive according to Szilard's will, and I can die according to his will as well.
私は生かされ
殺されもするということです
You're weak.
弱い… 200年をムダにしたな
You wasted these 200 years.
ゎしの200年の成果を見せてやる
I will show you the results of my 200 years.
Lまぁ‥
They are miserable people...
浅ましい連中だ
やはり手を出していたか
To think they took it after all...
何のことだ?
What are you talking about?
What's that all about?!
何だ それ !
そんな勝手な話があるか!
There's no way he can do that!
セラ一ドにとって私は
娘のようなものなのでしょう
I must be somewhat of a daughter in relation to Szilard.
A man who's able to kill his daughter at will and uses that as a threat to work you like a horse... That's not a father!
娘を勝手に殺せて
しかも それを脅しに
こき使う親なんているか!
と ぼけるな
Don't fool with me.
This was the Cure-All Elixir we all once drank.
これはかつて
我々が飲んだ 大いなる万能薬だ
I finally managed to make it on my own.
とうとう独力で完成させることに
成功したのだよ
あんたみたいな きれいなのが
あんな爺の娘のはずがない
Someone as beautiful as you just can't be that old man's daughter.
俺が保証してやる
That, I guarantee you.
随分お熱いこつたな
You two sure are lovey-dovey together.
フフツ
Dallas...
Yesterday's...
昨日の…
ダラス… どうしてここに?
Why are you here?
蔦いた ? 僕ね 不死身なんだよ
Are you surprised?
I am immortal.
知つてる 面白い
I know.
It's interesting.
In other words, I can strip your skin, I can gouge out your eyes,
つまり 生皮を罰がしたり
目玉を窒つたり
生きたまま心臓を握りつぶしたり しても
平気ということだよな?
and even if I rip out your heart and smash it, you will be just fine, right?
やればいいさ
そんな程度の苦しみは慣れきつている
Go ahead and do it.
I've long been used to such pain.
ほ~う
Have you ever been stuck in the eyes with a pair of heated tongs?
焼けた炙ぱ暑を目に
突き刺されたことがあるか?
酸の風呂に
つけられたことはあるか?
Have you ever been put in an acid bath?
生きたまま暖炉に
放り込まれたことは?
Have you ever been thrown into a fireplace alive?
And so I lived while a person, whom I had trusted, inflicted such pains on me every day.
私は自分の信じていた人間に毎日
そんな痛みを
与えられて生きてきたんだ
私は貴様のような暴力 には屈 しない
I won't yield to the violence a person like you can do to me.
My readiness for pain is different compared to yours!
お前なんかとは
痛みに対する覚悟が違うんだ!
ダメだな お前
You're so wrong.
はんちゆう
そんなのは趣味の範晴だ
You can categorize that as child's play.
Have you ever experienced someone skinning the flesh of your arm?
生きたまま腕の肉を丁寧に
剥力ヾされたことはあるか?
And then had someone carve some engravings in the bones of your arm?
そのまま腕の骨に
彫刻を入れられたことは?
中国の処刑法を知っているか?
You ever heard of that death penalty method the Chinese have?
巳本の拷問は ?
From my work, I know loads of different ways to torture someone in the Japanese style.
仕事柄 痛みを与える方法は
山ほど知つてる
殺すことを前提としたやつもな
Also those with murder as the premise.
チェスワフメイ工ル
Czeslaw Meyer, it seems that you indeed have, to a certain extent, prepared yourself for pain.
確かにお前は ある程度の痛みには
覚悟を抱い乙るようだ
But what was that scent of anxiety I felt in your eyes when I, Rail Tracer, stood before you?
だが俺を見た時の…
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一を前にした時の…
お前の目 に浮かんだ不安の色は何だ ?
What you fear... is the way!
お前が恐れているのは未知だ
You are thinking there might be extents of pain and anguish you have yet to experience.
自分の知らない所に
いまだかつて味わったことのない
痛みや苦しみが
あるのかもしれないと者えている
Let me inflict those on you.
俺がお前に与えてやろう
未知の痛みを
The way of pain.
Until you forget how to come back to life!
生き返り方を忘れるまでな
黒服が勝手にいなくなるなんて
俺ら ついてたな
We sure got lucky when those black-suits suddenly disappeared.
Indeed... So now we can...
そうだな てなゎけで そろそろ…
Okay! Give us your money!
よ一し お前ら金を出せ !
Not just your money, show us your tits as well!
金だけじやなく貴重品もな一
うわつ
ぐゎつ
この列車は
僕たちが占拠しました!
We have taken control of this train now!
If you don't want to die, follow our orders obediently!
死にたくなければ おとなしく
指示に従つて下さい!
Isn't that a bit too...
うが それは言いすきじや…
ジヤグジ一!
Jacuzzi!
驚かせてしまいましたね
I suppose we surprised you there.
これは… どういうことですか?
What... is going on here?!
I had heard the stories,
話には聞いていたが
目の当たりにするのは初めてだ
but this is the first time I've seen it for myself.
これはこれは
ドンバ丿し卜ロ丿しノラ一夕
Well, well, if it isn't Don Baltro Runorata.
It has been a while, Luck Gandor.
久しいな ラツクガンド一ル…
まずは うちの不始末を謂ぴよう
Let me first apologize for the misconduct on our side.
恐縮です
That's very kind of you.
However, for Don Runorata to come over himself... What brought that about?
しかし ドン丿しノラ一夕
自らお越しとは
どういう風の吹き回しで ?
It just means it's that big of a deal.
それだけ棗壺だといぅことだ
The secret you three are carrying, that is.
君 らの抱えた秘密がな
Let me get to the point.
単刀直入に言おう
うちの傘下に入りたまえ
Come work for me.
悪いようにはしない
I won't treat you badly.
I refuse.
お断りします
I wouldn't want to be treated as a guinea pig.
実験材料にされるのは
願い下げですので
フツ ならば妥協点はー つ‥
Then, there's only one point left to discuss.
ダラスジ工ノア一ドを引き渡せ
Hand over Dallas Genoard.
そうすれば二度と君らに
干渉はしない…
If you do that, I won't interfere with you any longer.
どうかね?
What do you think?
どうも気が進まない
ご提案です力ヾ…
It's a proposal that just doesn't sit right with me.
Where is Dallas now?
ダラスは今 どこにいるのだ ?
dokomade mo tsuzuiteru hoshizora miagete utau
I sing, looking up into the endless starry night.
kagiriaru bokutachi no eien wo yume miru melody
A melody in a dream... about our limited eternity.
mune ni afureru itoshisa no mizu wa
This water of love, overflowing from my chest...
mirai no hate de dareka ni todoku darou
I wonder if it will reach someone in the future?
shinjite iruyo
I will believe in you.
harukana toki wo kake nukete
Transcending generations of time...
bokutachi no yobigoe wa itsuka ookina uta ni naru
Will our calls turn into a beautiful song one day?
ai wo tsumuide yukeru yo
You can start building your love,
ima wa mada konnani chiisana hikari dakedo
Though right now, the light is still faint.
Next ep
Preview
Firo and the Three Gandor Brothers Are Felled
by Assassins' Bullets
What should we do, Miria?!
It says here that Firo and the Gandor brothers will fall to murderous bullets!
It's terrible!
Firo and Luck and...
Firo and Luck and Berga and...
And...
Ehmm, anyway, it's terrible!
I can't remember, but anyway, it's terrible!